I'm completely out of cigarettes.
Looks like the world's gone all blurry
from the lack of nicotine in me.
Hello there, Yaniko.
Uh…
I'm the cigarette fairy.
When Beast Folk are in need, I arrive to
save them from the chains of nicotine…
Yeah, I know a thing in heaven!
Oh, I need a bath reason number
215 for why I hate Beast Folk!
Friendly tip, Chainsmoker.
I can see you're having
a nicotine overdose.
You're forgetting the enjoy responsibly
in moderation part of smoking!
That's exactly what I'm doing!
I must say, you sound completely
responsible and in control.
Oh, all right.
It would seem we've reached an impasse.
Thus, I shall bestow upon you the
sacred nicotine receptor exercise.
Ah, ah, dokoi dokoi.
Dokoi dokoi dokoi dokoi se!
What do you think? Is it working?
Stop!
Don't give it to the diggity!
Your fault for shaking that toasty little
booty in my face, so don't run away!
Goddammit, I can't taste this cigarette!
Of course you can't!
After all, I'm just in your...
Hello?
Right here.
Fresh newsletter after all of nothing
more than a figment of your imagination?
Yaniko
You all right we can't be I can
feel you right here with me?
Even so it's nothing more than an
illusion created by your brain.
Don't say that.
That's not true
The smell of smoke.
The feeling of hemp a
sunset reflecting off
the land and the distant
whistle of a tree?
Don't you see?
I can never leave this place.
We'll be together forever!
So let's do that exercise.
Ah!
And one, and one A hot na be,
you
so
much
for watching.
I want to do it as long as it kills me.
If you want to do it, the way I am.
I don't want to lose my legs.
I don't want to be seen anymore.
I don't want to lose
my
legs.
Hey, Yaku Neko.
I'm running crazy, you're the one you
can see, and let me put my smoke off you!
Hey, what's up?
Sorry, but if you're looking
for cigs, I'm fresh out.
Liar, you're smoking one right now.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, this.
Is that not a hand-rolled cig?
Uh-huh.
Give me a puff.
Well, the thing is...
Come on, don't be stingy.
I've treated you to plenty of my
cigarette butts back when you were broke.
Hang on, wait a sec.
Jeez, talk about an
ungrateful little junior.
But that's not...
God damn, that shit's dank. Aw, man.
Senpai, if you're gonna hit it, you
gotta hold that shit in for a sec.
Otherwise, you're wasting
the good stuff, trust me.
Is this a cigarette? Sure it is.
This is some good stuff
you got here, Yaku.
Just gas, right?
Oh, Senpai, let's get some ice cream.
It tastes great if you eat it right now.
This is a cigarette?
Of course it is!
Jane Smoker Cat!
Is it that time of the year already?
Ugh, I hate how the meds
always taste like yenshin tea.
Yaku, mind if I come in?
What are you doing?
Oh, oh, um, hey, sup, howdy.
I wanted to take my mad beast prevention
meds, but I didn't have any water.
The utilities cut me off
again for not paying.
Uh, yeah.
I just took my meds, too.
I didn't ask, but okay.
There's no way you're shooting
up any weird drugs again, right?
Of course I'm not doing drugs!
I'm clean now and you
fucking know it, don't you?
Oh, goddammit, Senpai!
If you don't believe me,
then who the fuck will?
I'll be all alone!
I thought I could just live like everybody
else if I finally just got clean!
My life is bullshit!
Okay, real fast.
Quick question for you.
You care a lot about me.
Why?
Oh, I get it.
I don't lie!
You're a fucking narc, aren't you?
Good skies, piggy!
Now, give me back my
senpai, you fucking f**k!
Cops like you are the reason
my life's gone to sh**!
So just show your true colors already!
Chainsmoker Cat!
Oh, but man, that show is funny, right?
Who knew he could drink that much?
Beast folk, spare a moment of your time.
Yeah, the bar owner
was fucking crazy, man.
Yeah, I didn't think he'd
flash his ass like that.
It'll be worth your while.
Huh?
Looking for excitement?
How about a palm reading?
Goddamn, that's pricey!
It's probably a waste of time.
I'll do one for a hundred yen, though.
I'll consider it for the chance to
wipe those cocky grins off your faces
That sounds fun.
If you see my truth by
the end of the reading,
I want full payment Oh, that's fine by me
Oh, the smell.
Forget fortune-telling and tell
you how to wash your hands.
Yeah
A smoker, I see.
You're severely addicted and
your family longs to free you
from this nicotine curse It
seems you're a stranger to money,
so you live alone in a slum.
And what's worse,
lung cancer will take you in five years,
or you'll burn alive from smoking.
Oh, Poet-senpai, she's
just a creepy old lady.
Here you go.
Take a big tasty puff.
Appears I was correct.
All right, you're next, kitty.
don't be afraid I'll do yours for
a hundred yen huh oh hi me all this
kind of oogie-boogie stuff is a hard
no your mystic mumbo-jumbo is based
on the Barnum effect if you just open
your eyes and look around you it's
easy to guess stuff about people are
you currently taking any illegal drugs
of course not then do you have a
criminal record no way house has never
been searched?
No, never.
Are you being truthful?
A thousand percent.
I don't get it. Who knew my
palm had such a big mouth?
I mean, not like I did
anything wrong, though.
You get to decide whether
you believe it or not.
If you like what you heard, just leave
a hundred yen and be on your way.
Huh? Ah!
Chainsmoker cat!
Bye.
Senpai, don't you need to work?
Everything has its time.
My part-time job pays
at the end of each day.
You want to come with?
Listen, Yaku.
You see that cloud?
Aww.
That's what I'm gonna be.
A being of freedom, not bound by
the crudities of our mortal realm.
That's the kind of me that I want to be.
Something as banal as hunger will
never take away that freedom from me.
That!
That's so cool!
You're a Buddha, monk, and
Stoic sage all wrapped in a one!
Well, I guess even a cloud could get
moving if they ran out of cigarettes.
That's when I'll consider
your offer. Sure!
I'll make it happen!
Today, Senpai brings back memories.
Makes me think of when we first met.
And how cool you were.
That's right.
You were as cool as that cloud in the sky.
And there was nothing in the
world that could hold you down.
I loved that.
I know you're in there, Yakuza!
Open the fuck up already!
Help me get a job, goddammit!
No, you're not asleep.
You better not be on any
fucking drugs, you hear me?
Wake up and open the door! What?
It's the middle of the night.
Oh, it's bad.
It's really, really bad.
Because I thought I had a carton,
but I smoked it last week.
I need money to buy cigarettes ASAP.
Help me get a job so I can
start a campaign right away!
I'm living in!
Ah, I get it.
She's not a cloud in the sky.
She's just a cloud of smoke.
This game sucks!
Oh my God, this game fucking
sucks! Come on, Yanni.
Lesson number one with fighting
games is you don't lose your temper.
Emotions get in your way.
You gotta channel it into focus, yeah?
If I could do that, I wouldn't be
suffering like this. It's my turn!
I'll teach you how to
play ranked mode matches.
I've got Ultimate Master Rank on this
game and I can show you how I did it.
Sit back and prepare to be wowed.
No, wait, crap.
You must have picked
Shenlong to stand a chance.
You piece of shit, gloom-eating
Neko Boonga, motherfucker!
Anyway, Yanni, are you hungry?
Why don't we take a break
and make some lunch?
Yeah, I think I've got some
ramen hiding somewhere.
Either way, since we're opening
up about our feelings...
Would you quit smoking in
the fucking video game room?!
I'm so sorry!
And then, and then, my
slipper went flying!
Seriously, there's no way!
No, really, I mean it!
You know, you're nothing like any
other beast folk I've ever met.
You can let your cat's side out with us.
Oh, well, each of us is different
when it comes to stuff like that.
Did you just meow?
Come on, stop it.
There's the kitty cat.
It's the Fluffy Puppy Pup!
It's my cute little sister, Nyah!
What's up, Nyah?
Heading back home from school, Nyah?
I didn't know you had a pig, sis.
I am all about this meowing.
She's so cute!
You're not gonna pay attention.
I'm sorry, have we met?
Hey! Hamehame! Hello, chat!
It's time for Hamei
Channel, guys! Who's ready?
Hamei-chan's so glad
everyone came to watch!
By the way, guess what?
I wanted to tell you all!
Hamei-chan had something
terrible happen to her today!
No!
A crane fly? Ah!
Get away from me!
Hamei-chan doesn't like
flying, little creepy crawlies!
You're such a meanie,
Mr. Buggywug! Fine, then!
I'm gonna use the vacuum cleaner on you!
I'm sorry, Chad!
I gotta stop this dream for a second!
I can't believe her!
I just can't believe her!
She's a complete and utter embarrassment!
Wow.
I didn't know you hated
your sister so much.
I don't hate her.
So you like her, then?
Mmm.
Like her?
I don't know!
I-I-I don't feel too good.
Whoa, sorry, Imoko.
I'm sure it's just a
complicated situation, right?
I don't know!
Seriously, we're sorry.
That's so impressive you
can get that loud, Imoko.
Cigarettes and coffee are a perfect match,
but I hate how it makes me wanna pee.
Well,
I think hate is a bit strong for me, but
I do get about it making you want to pee.
What do you mean?
Hamai-chan doesn't understand.
Maybe you two just have
hamster-sized bladders is all.
What do you mean by that,
little Miss Toilet Fairy?
Miss Toilet Fairy?
What do you mean by that?
This girl, in high school, she used
to always eat lunch on the toilet.
We tried to get her to join us,
but she wouldn't come out, so people
started calling her the Toilet Fairy?
or Tori for short.
I'm out of death! Stop it!
She said leave me alone or I'll
unleash the eighth plague of Egypt!
I'm begging you to please
stop talking about that!
Oh, no!
You're dead!
I mean, Hami-chan is an idol
the whole world looks up to,
so she doesn't do nasty
things like peeing.
But Yakuko does.
You heard what she said, Senpai.
so hold her down for me, okay?
Ah!
Wait!
What are you -
Turn out!
Stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
The old eighth plague of Egypt, huh?
Senpai, this frog-looking thing
here, that's the real Toilet Fairy.
Ugh.
Goddamn, you're gross.
I'll kill you, you goddamn motherfucker!
Why is it so bitter salty?
You fucking junkie!
Enjoy the taste of life itself!
Puke them, you fucking pussy!
What?
Is that all you fucking...
You know, I'd really appreciate it
if they didn't do this in my room.
Chain smoker cat!
I went to City Hall today.
Hame Neko's finally getting
herself a last name.
But when both your parents are beast
folk, you don't grow up with one.
She's always getting five points knocked
off her grades because she didn't have one.
Done!
Look, Yonny-nyon! Look, look!
Hame-chan has a last name!
Hm?
What is that?
Isn't it the cutest thing ever?
From now on, Hame's real
name is Hameko Yurifua Angel!
Nice to meet you, Yonny-nyon!
Hey, I don't know. It's kind of gross.
It's long and kind of hard to say. What?
You really mean it?
I'm willing to bet nobody will ever say
your full name with a last name like that.
What?
You mean me?
Well, then how come you've never
told me your last name, Yanin Yan?
I bet it's because it's
a really weird one.
Oh, it's Sato.
That's painfully normal!
I hear it gets way harder to fix your
name after you've already changed it once.
So now's your chance to fix it
before you turn in the paperwork.
I'll be fine.
I'm gonna submit it as is.
How's Hameko Tanaka sound? Oh, hell no!
Okay, you should be all set
You'll receive the official
documents in the mail.
So please come back to
this counter to change
your identification card
once you've received them
Just leave me alone.
Um, what are we doing?
This situation?
Let me take a look, huh?
What's with this last name?
Well, a lot of beast folk have fairly
unusual names by our standards.
This symbol though—is that a drawing?
What does it mean?
She left before I could
ask how to read it.
I
wonder what language that could be.
But we can't put any drawings
or symbols into the system.
system Oh, I think I got it.
It could possibly be a butthole? Huh?
I guess so.
Looks like an anus.
Well, then do I enter anus
or butthole into this system?
Neither of them flow particularly well.
How about anal?
Maybe I'll do a surprise stream to
celebrate my new last name when I get home!
Hameko Yurifua Angel!
And thus, Hameko Yurifua
Anal Angel was born
Thank you.
And why is this so human being?
I am out of it, and I'm not working.
I'm not using that.
I'm using that same stuff.
Same people who like
the person who can live.
I'm just trying to get more than anything.
Have you been doing this?
This place isn't still a rush.
I don't want to worry too.
Thank you.